[
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"2 + 5 x 6 = ?", "answer":0, "answers":["32"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"2.7182 is the approximation for which variable used in logarithms?", "answer":0, "answers":["E"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"A line drawn from an angle of a triangle to the mid_point of the opposite side is a(n) _______.", "answer":0, "answers":["Median"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"A line drawn from an angle of a triangle to the mid-point of the opposite side is a(n) _______.", "answer":0, "answers":["Median"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"A triangle with three equal sides is called _______.", "answer":0, "answers":["Equilateral"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"A triangle with two equal sides is called __________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Isosceles"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"An angle greater than 180 degrees and less than 360 degrees is a(n) ________ angle.", "answer":0, "answers":["Reflex"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"An angle greater than 90 degrees and less than 180 degrees is said to be _________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Obtuse"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"An angle greater than 90 degrees is said to be _________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Obtuse"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"An integer that is greater than 1 and is divisible only by itself and 1 is known as a(n) _______.", "answer":0, "answers":["Prime"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"Approximately how many inches are there in one meter", "answer":0, "answers":["39"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"Approximately how many inches are there in one meter?", "answer":0, "answers":["Thirty nine"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"Arc, radius, and sector are parts of a(n) _________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Circle"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"Benoit Mandelbrot discovered what mathematical structures?", "answer":0, "answers":["Fractals"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"He is known as \"The Father of Geometry\".", "answer":0, "answers":["Euclid"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"How many corners are there in a cube", "answer":0, "answers":["Eight"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"How many corners are there in a cube?", "answer":0, "answers":["Eight"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"How many different letters are used in the roman numeral system?", "answer":0, "answers":["Seven"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"How many nickles are there in $2.25", "answer":0, "answers":["45"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"How many nickles are there in 2.25?", "answer":0, "answers":["Forty five"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"If you count from 1 to 100, how many 7's will you come across?", "answer":0, "answers":["20"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"If you cut through a solid sphere what shape will the flat area be", "answer":0, "answers":["Circle"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"If you cut through a solid sphere what shape will the flat area be?", "answer":0, "answers":["Circle"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"Name the number system which uses only the symbols 1 and 0.", "answer":0, "answers":["The binary system"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"Solve this: 10*3+2?", "answer":0, "answers":["32"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"The angles inside a square total _______ degrees.", "answer":0, "answers":["360"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"The first antiderivative of acceleration is:", "answer":0, "answers":["Velocity"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"The mathematical study of properties of lines, angels, etc., is ________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Geometry"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"The space occupied by a body is called its ______.", "answer":0, "answers":["Volume"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"The square root of 1 is?", "answer":0, "answers":["1"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"Two angles that total 180 degrees are called _______.", "answer":0, "answers":["Supplementary"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"What geometric shape has 4 equal sides", "answer":0, "answers":["Square"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"What geometric shape has 4 equal sides?", "answer":0, "answers":["Square"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"What is 65% of 60?", "answer":0, "answers":["39"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"What is next in the series 1 8 27 ?? 125 216?", "answer":0, "answers":["64"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"What is the maximum number of integer degrees in a reflex angle?", "answer":0, "answers":["359"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"What is the maximum number of integer degrees in an acute angle?", "answer":0, "answers":["89"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"What is the maximum number of integer degrees in an obtuse angle?", "answer":0, "answers":["179"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"What is the minimum number of integer degrees in a reflex angle?", "answer":0, "answers":["181"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"What is the minimum number of integer degrees in an acute angle?", "answer":0, "answers":["One"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"What is the minimum number of integer degrees in an obtuse angle?", "answer":0, "answers":["91"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"What is the name given to a curve that approaches a line, but never quite touches it?", "answer":0, "answers":["Asymptote"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"What is the name given to the number equal to 10 raised to the power of 100?", "answer":0, "answers":["A \"googol\""], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"What is the only digit that has the same number of letters as its value?", "answer":0, "answers":["Four"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"What is the square root of -1 ?", "answer":0, "answers":["I"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"What is the square root of one quarter?", "answer":0, "answers":["One half"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"What is x to the power of zero equal to?", "answer":0, "answers":["One"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"Who invented logarithms ?", "answer":0, "answers":["John Napier"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"MATHEMATICS", "lang":"en", "tags":["MATHEMATICS"], "question":"Who proved Fermat's Last Theorem ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Andrew Wiles"], "source":""}
]
